societeperrier.com 2012-09-15

# Privacy Policy | Société Perrier

## The Source for Nightlife & Culture

Mirrorball Group LLC (“Company”) has created this consumer privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our practices regarding information collection and use solely for the web site located at www.societeperrier.com (the "Service"). By using or accessing or using the Service, you signify your agreement to be bound by our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SERVICE.

Thank you for visiting this Nestlé Waters North America Inc. (also referred to as “we,’ “us,” and “our”) website. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we want to keep your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy describes our information practices. By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy before you submit any personal information on this website.  
What information about customers do we gather?

## Personal information

To simply browse our website, we do not ask you to provide any personal information. However, if you wish to participate in many of the features and services offered on our website, we may ask you to provide certain personally identifiable and/or demographic information. Personally identifiable information, as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to any information that can be used to personally identify you or contact you. This may include, for example, your name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number, as well as demographic information that is linked to personally identifiable information. Demographic information, as used in this Privacy Policy, refers to information that describes personal characteristics but could not, on its own, be used to personally identify you or contact you. Demographic information may include your date of birth, age, gender, habits, or preferences.

Personally identifiable information and/or demographic information are only collected when you voluntarily provide it to us through one of the online forms available on this website, which may be most commonly encountered when:

purchasing products or services from this website;  
registering or signing up for membership on this website;  
posting comments on message boards and other interactive discussion forms;  
responding to surveys;  
participating in sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions;  
registering for newsletters or other communications from us; or  
any other interaction that requires the submission of personal information.  
If demographic information is collected for an activity or service that also requires personally identifiable information, we may combine the demographic information with your personally identifiable information. Combining this data allows us to customize the notices we send you and the content we provide you according to your interests and preferences.

## Non-personal information

## Cookies

We use cookies to improve the use and functionality of our website. A cookie is a small file that websites often store on a user’s computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient way for us to personalize or enhance your experience on our website and to make your next visit more enjoyable. For example, cookies may allow us to remember the content you previously viewed on our website or your log-in information. Cookies may also be used to remember items you have previously placed in your shopping cart when making purchases. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information, however we may link information contained in a cookie to personally identifiable information collected from you by other means (e.g., website registration).  
You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, if you do so, you may not be able to register on our website or use other features that require registration or the collection of information.

## IP Addresses

We may keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to, among other things: (i) troubleshoot technical concerns; (ii) maintain website safety and security; (iii) restrict access to our website to certain users, and (iv) better understand how our website is utilized. An IP address is a number used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

## Log Files

We, or a vendor on our behalf, may collect information in the form of logs, files that record website activity and gather statistics about web users’ browsing habits. These entries are generated anonymously and help us gather, among other things: (i) a user’s browser type and operating system; (ii) information about a user’s session (such as the URL they came from, the date and time they visited our website, and which pages they have viewed on our site and for how long); and (iii) other similar navigational data. We may also use information captured in log files for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve and customize the online services we provide you. Log files are used internally only and are not associated with any particular user.

## Web Beacons

We may use web beacons on our website or include them in e-mail messages we send you. Web beacons are small strings of programming code that provide a method of delivering a graphic image on a web page or e-mail message for the purposes of transferring data back to us. Web beacons may be used to allow us, or our advertising delivery partners, to communicate with cookies stored on your computer. The information collected via web beacons may also include some of the information described in the IP Address section above, as well as information about how a user responds to an e-mail campaign (such as, the time the e-mail is opened, where does the user link to from the e-mail, etc.). We use web beacon information for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to, site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, advertising and e-mail auditing and reporting, and content personalization.

## How do we use the information we collect?

Generally, all information collected is used for the purpose for which the information was collected or as otherwise identified at the point of collection or in this Privacy Policy. For example, if you register or open an account on this website, the information you provide may be used to offer you the benefits and privileges that typically come along with registration. This may include purchasing products and/or services, access to and use of exclusive or personalized content or activities (such as message boards), participation in special events and promotions (contests, sweepstakes, coupons, etc.), and the ability to receive any communications or marketing material you select at the time of registration or that automatically come with registration. Similarly, if you contact us via an online contact form, your information may be used to respond to your inquiry or comment, and in some instances, post the answers to your question in anonymous form on the website. Any credit card information you provide us is used to fulfill and process your online purchases.

When providing information on our website, you may also be given the option (through a check box or otherwise) to have your information used for an activity or service different from the primary activity or service that you are requesting. For example, if you are signing up for a contest or other promotion, you may also be able to sign up for newsletters or alerts from this website or our partners. If you choose to receive these additional services, we will use your information to provide them to you.

From time to time, we may be approached by reputable third party companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To extend these products or services to you, we may use your personally identifiable information to send out notices on their behalf. We see this as a value-added service helping you find useful products or services. Our goal is to limit the notices and communications to those that we think you would appreciate receiving. Please note that all such mailings come strictly from us and your personally identifiable information is not shared with these other companies.

We may also use your personal and/or demographic information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve, personalize, and customize the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. This may include occasionally combining, updating, or otherwise enhancing the personally identifiable information collected through this website with data we receive from outside records or third parties.

The following provides additional information about certain features of our website.

## Newsletters and E-mail

If you provide us your e-mail address and/or mailing address, the contact information you provide may be used to send you newsletters, product or service literature, or other communications that you request.

In addition, you may receive communications introducing you to other Nestlé brands or websites.

We may also use your e-mail address to send you transactional or administrative communications (e.g., confirmation e-mail when you make an online purchase or sign up for, or unsubscribe from, a service or activity), as well as certain service-related announcements. Collectively, these types of communications are referred to in this Privacy Policy as “Administrative Communications.”

## Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions

To enter an online sweepstakes, contest, or promotion (collectively “Promotions”), you may be required to first register on this website. The information collected as part of a Promotion is used to determine your eligibility, notify you whether you are a winner, and/or fulfill and deliver prizes. We may use third party service providers to operate sweepstakes. In these instances, we may share the information collected for the Promotion with that third party, so that it may perform tasks necessary to provide the sweepstakes. If you are a winner, certain information about you (such as your name and picture) may be posted to the website. For more information about Promotions, please see the official rules or details posted with a specific Promotion.

## Surveys

There are two types of surveys that may be conducted on this website. One is where purely demographic or survey information (such as age, gender, household information, and other interests, etc.) is requested and the information is not linked to any personally identifiable information about you. In other cases (such as during website registration), we may collect the same information and combine it with your personally identifiable information.

## Message Boards and other interactive features

Visitors may post reviews, comments, and other content; send e-cards and other communications; and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "Spam". You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a card or other content. We reserve the right (but do not have the obligation) to remove or edit such content, but do not regularly review posted content.

We encourage you to be wary of giving out personally identifiable information or images about yourself in public areas such as on a message board or other online community feature. Such information can be collected and used by people you do not know. As such, we cannot guarantee the security and privacy of, and are not responsible for, any information you post in these areas. Your use of these features is at your own risk. Please note that if you choose to post a picture or message through one of these features, we may post, along with the picture or message, certain non-personally identifiable information about you, such as your username and/or city and state of residence.

If you do post content or submit material, you grant us and our affiliates a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant us and our affiliates and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if they choose. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify Nestlé Waters North America Inc. or its affiliates for all claims resulting from content you supply. Nestlé Waters North America Inc. has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. Nestlé Waters North America Inc. takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any content posted by you or any third party.

This website may also provide one-time use interactive features, such as e-cards and tell-a-friend messages. Personally identifiable information requested for an e-card, tell-a-friend message, or other referral feature, or other one-time use features (typically, e-mail addresses and names) will be used on a one-time basis (e.g., to send the communication) and will not be further retained by Nestlé Waters North America Inc.

## Purchasing Products and Services Online

This website may allow you to purchase Nestlé products or services through an online store operated by Nestlé Waters North America Inc. or a vendor on our behalf, as well as provide links to unaffiliated third party sites that sell Nestlé products. If you are purchasing a product or service through a Nestlé Waters North America Inc. website, you will be asked to provide your credit card information, including credit card number and billing and shipping addresses, as well as other basic contact information (e.g., telephone number and e-mail address). This information is used to fulfill your purchase and confirm your order.

If the online store you are visiting is operated by an unaffiliated third party, we may provide you a direct link to the third party store for your convenience. Please note, however, that these sites are not operated by Nestlé Waters North America Inc. and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of the online store you are visiting before sharing any personally identifiable information or sensitive information such as your credit card number.

## Who is collecting your information and is it shared with anyone?

The information that you disclose on this website is collected by Nestlé Waters North America Inc. or by a vendor acting on its behalf; and is used in accordance with the practices set forth above. The following provides more specific information about how and to whom we may disclose your information.

## Agents and Contractors

We may use outside companies, agents, or contractors (collectively “vendors”) to provide support for the internal operations of our websites and to assist us with administering e-commerce services or various other programs and promotions available on our website. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payment and providing customer service. In the course of doing so, these vendors may come into contact with your personal information. However, we only give them access to (or allow them to collect on our behalf) the information they need in order to perform the specific tasks they have been hired to do. They may not use it for other purposes.

## Third Party Ad Networks

This site may utilize third party web beacons to help manage online advertising. These web beacons are provided by our advertising delivery partners. These pixels enable our partners to recognize a unique cookie on your computer, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website as well as provide you with targeted advertisements. The information we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. For more information regarding third party web beacons and cookies or to opt out of targeted advertisements delivered by our advertising delivery partners, go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

## Partners, Affiliates and Joint Promotions

From time to time, we may run a joint or co-sponsored program or promotion on our websites with another company, organization, affiliate or other reputable third party; and, as part of this event, collect and process personally identifiable information. You can tell when another company or business is involved in our promotions or your transactions and we may share customer information related to those transactions with that company or business. Periodically, we may run a promotion on our website that features the products or services of another company and may give you the opportunity to opt in to receive information directly from that third party company.

When operating any promotion involving another company, we may provide a separate link to that company’s website. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a company other than Nestlé Waters North America Inc., you can always choose not to opt in or participate in these events at the time the information is collected/ requested. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any of these businesses or individuals or the content of their websites. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, content of all these and any other third parties. We encourage you to carefully review their privacy policies and other conditions of use.

## Legal and Business Transfers

We may also disclose personally identifiable information if we are required to do so by law, or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes, to respond to any claims, or to protect the safety or rights of Nestlé Waters North America Inc., its customers, or the public.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, personally identifiable information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event of a merger or acquisition of all or part of Nestlé Waters North America Inc. or Nestlé by another company, or in the event that Nestlé Waters North America Inc. or Nestlé were to sell or dispose of all or a part of the Nestlé business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by that Nestlé business, which could include personally identifiable information, subject to applicable law. Similarly, personally identifiable information may be transferred as part of a corporate reorganization, insolvency proceeding, or other similar event, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

## Aggregate Information

We may share aggregated demographic or survey information with third parties, but this information is in anonymous form and does not contain any personally identifiable information. The aggregate information that we share may include anonymous information that is captured through the use of cookies and other similar tracking technology, as discussed in the Non-personal information section above.

## What safeguards do we use to protect your personal information?

Nestlé Waters North America Inc. takes commercially reasonable effects to protect the confidentiality and security of the personal information collected from our website visitors. These efforts may include, but are not necessarily limited to: (i) storing your personal information in secure operating environments; (ii) using industry standard SSL encryption to protect the security of certain sensitive personal information (such as credit card information) during transmission to our websites; and (iii) verifying the identities of registered website users before they can access the personal information we maintain about them.

If you use this site to access your online account, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.

## What choices do I have?

The following outlines the choices you have with respect to the collection and use of your personal information by Nestlé Waters North America Inc.

You always have the option not to share any of your personal information with us. However, if you choose this option, you will be limited in the activities and features we can provide you.

If you do not want to receive newsletters, announcements, or other communications and/or services from this website, please opt out from these communications or services at the time of registration or when the information is collected. If you have opted in and, at a later time, wish to opt out, you may update your profile on the website and amend your preferences or contact us a the address below.

Along with e-mail marketing communication sent to you, we will provide you the opportunity to discontinue receiving future marketing communications (i.e., unsubscribe). Simply follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail.

You can always review or update any personal information that we may have collected about you for our general website registration by visiting the appropriate update profile sections of the website.

If any of the mechanisms set forth above is not available or you wish to make a different request, please contact as at:  
Nestlé Waters North America Inc.  
900 Long Ridge Road, Building 2  
Stamford, CT 06902

Please note that regardless of your opt out selections, we reserve the right to continue sending you Administrative Communications if you have previously provided your information in connection with any one of our online features, activities, or services.

In addition, please note that if you participated in a promotion or program that involved a third party company and, as part of that promotion, you agreed to receive future communications directly from that third party, you will need to contact the third party (not Nestlé Waters North America Inc.) directly to opt out from such communications. This process may be outlined in the third party’s privacy policy.

## Children

This website is a general audience website. We do not sell products for purchase by children or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should always get their parent's or guardian's consent before providing information to anyone via the Internet. If you are under the age of 13, you should not register or provide any information on our Web site. We do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

## Terms and Conditions, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit our site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Connecticut, as set forth in our Terms and Conditions. If you have any concern about privacy on our site, please send us a thorough description to the address below and we will try to resolve it.

The Nestlé Waters North America Inc.  
900 Long Ridge Road, Building 2  
Stamford, Connecticut 06902

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you come back to this website to make sure you are aware of any changes and how your information may be used. Your continued use of this website signifies your acceptance of these changes.
